TOOL SHORT · CREATE New class. New test.
One sentence.
validateNewObject CLAS/OC · ZCL_HELLO · ZDEMO
resolveTransport ZDEMO → DEVK900124
createObject ZCL_HELLO
setObjectSource activate=true
createTestInclude ltc_hello
unitTestRun ZCL_HELLO
created outside the stateful session · readable at once
ABAP Unit 1 passed · 0 failed Transport DEVK900124 Status ZCL_HELLO active
Validate, transport, create, test. In order.
validateNewObject ZCL_HELLO · destination=PRD
kind "policyDenied" gate readOnly destination PRD hint PRD is readOnly; create refused before any SAP call
Guard rails live in the server, not in the host.
Objects, created.
The server knows the order, and where it must not write.
validateNewObject resolveTransport createObject
unitTestRun
github.com/williansaez/abap-adt-mcp